Huth, Geoffrey A.; Papers mss137
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, 1965-1966; 1969-2006; 12; 30.75 cubic ft.
  - Paper Publications, 1965-1966; 1969; 1972-2006; 12.1; 28.5 cubic ft.
    - Helmes, Scott, Non Additive Postulations and Other Poems, 2000 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 106)
    - Helsem, Michael, Beyond Endurance, 1990 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 107)
    - Helsem, Michael, Giyorbicon: Volquardsen svinmol; chabd, haply yallifer, 1990 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 108)
    - Hennigar, Sean, telegram to the dog's shadow, 1990 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 109)
    - Hibbard, Tom, Brief Eternities, 1989 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 110)
    - Hibbard, T., Flowers, Clouds, 1987 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 111)
    - Hibbard, Tom, untitled collage, 1986 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 112)
    - Hibbard, Tom, untitled collage, 1986 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 113)
    - Higgins, Dick, Scenes Forgotten and Otherwise Remembered, 1998 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 114)
    - Higgins, Dick, snowflake: on turning forty, 1978 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 115)
    - Higgins, Dick, Some Poetry Intermedia, 1976 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 116)
    - Higginson Journal #48, 1987 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 117)
    - Hill, Crag, 3 from DICT, ca. 1987 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 118)
    - Hill, Crag, American Standard, 1989 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 119)
    - Hill, Crag, Animal Identity, 1989 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 120)
    - Hill, Crag, Corporate Profile, 1984 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 121)
    - Hill, Crag, Designs for Rubberstamps, ca. 1989 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 122)
    - Hill, Crag, HOR, 1986 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 123)
    - Hill, Crag, Score Profile, 1985 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 124)
    - Hill, Crag, Take into Account, 1987 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 125)
    - Hill, Crag, the Third day, 1984 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 126)
    - Hill, Crag, The Week, 1991 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 127)
    - Hill-Kaucher, Jennifer, Book of Days, gift of author, 2005 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 128)
    - Hill-Kaucher, Jennifer, for The Fall Leaves Variations, kite tail press #15, 2006 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 129)
    - Hill-Kaucher, Jennifer, for The Fall Leaves Variations, kite tail press #18, 2006 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 130)
    - Hill-Kaucher, Jennifer, Questioning Walls Open, gift of author, 2001 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 131)
    - Hill, Sean Wolf, The Hoosier Poet Pilgrimage, 1987 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 132)
    - Hill, Sean Wolf, Waterland Lost, 1987 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 133)
    - The Hiram Poetry Review, #42, 1987 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 134)
    - Hlavsa, Virginia V., Festillifes, 1992 (Box 8 (Go-Hl) (12-Publications), Folder 135)
    - Holdstock, PJ, Mouths of the Amazon, 1995 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Hollowpoint, #'s1-4, Undated (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Holmes, Mimi, A Selection of Selves, 1991 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Holmes, Mimi, A Selection of Selves, 1991 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Hood, Wharton, untitled, 1991 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Hood, Wharton, Abscess, inscribed and autographed, 1989 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Hood, Wharton, Advertisement, 1990 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Hood, Wharton, brushed with greatness, Undated (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Hood, Wharton, ed. Do You Read Your Garbage?, 2001 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Hood, Wharton, evening horizon, 1987 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Hood, Wharton, haiku, 1986 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Hood, Wharton, the harp, ca. 1988 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Hood, Wharton, ill airport, 1986 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Hood, Wharton, House of Cards, Undated (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Hood, Wharton and Brendan Donegan, Near Huronia, ca. 1988 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Hood, Wharton, Nelinski in Toronto, 1988 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 16)
    - Hood, Wharton, the roads to follow, 1989 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Hood, Wharton, saying nothing, 1991 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Hood, Wharton, slight light, 1991 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Horse-fly, Volume 1, #'s1-4, 1990 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Horse-fly, Volume 2, #'s1-4, 1990 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Hotel Dire, #5, 23, 666, 1991-1992 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Houedard, Dom Silvester, op and kinkon poems/and some non-kinkon, 1965 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Houedard, Dom Silvester, Vienna Circles, 1992 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Howling Dog, Volume 2, #2, Volume 3, #1, Volume 5, #2, 1986-1987; ca. 1989 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Hryciuk, Marshall, The Galloping Syntaxi Strands, 1992 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Hryciuk, Marshall, pink, 1987 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 27)
    - Hryciuk, Marshall, The Traveling Light, 1988 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 28)
    - Hryciuk, Marshall, eggshell interior (48), 1990 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 29)
    - Hubbard, Elbert, Initiative, Undated (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 30)
    - The Hudson Valley Regional Review, Volume 7, #2, 1990 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 31)
    - Human Documents, Tom Phillips' Art of the Page, 1993 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 32)
    - Hunter, Paul, Thefts of the Obvious, 1985 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 33)
    - Hunter, Paul, Wheeling We Invent New Leaders, 1985 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 34)
    - Huth, Erick, G., and Nini, The Mute Hemophiliac, 1987 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 35)
    - Huth, G., adam'sgift, 1992 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 36)
    - Huth, G., AND, 1991 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 37)
    - Huth, Geof, ed. &2: an/thology of pwoermds, 2004 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 38)
    - Huth, G., awe&3angle, 1988 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 39)
    - Huth, G., Analphabet, 1993 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 40)
    - Huth, Geof, Brain Cell Fractal, Undated (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 41)
    - Huth, G., The Butterfly Well & 4 Other Poems, 1988 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 42)
    - Huth, Geof, CAA Membership Guide 1995, Written, designed and illustrated by G. Huth, Undated (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 43)
    - Huth, Geof, Capital Area Archivists, brochure, Written, designed and illustrated by G. Huth, 1991 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 44)
    - Huth, G., c l o u d s, eight colors, 1986 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 45)
    - Huth, G., Dachau: afterwards, 1994 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 46)
    - Huth, Geof, Dirt, Issue #3, 2006 August (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 47)
    - Huth, G., "drift", 1991 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 48)
    - Huth, Geof A., Eugenio de Andrade Visits Albany, Poems-for-All #416, 2004 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 49)
    - Huth, Geof A., Eugenio de Andrade Visits Albany, Poems-for-All #417, Corrected reprint with out #416, 2004 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 50)
    - Huth, Geof, Felt (ifIfElTiT+ieNclRcled1), 2005 November (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 51)
    - Huth, Geof, forked lake, 2004 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 52)
    - Huth, Geof, "G. Huth", two different covers, 1989 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 53)
    - Huth, G., gGGoLDEND, 1988 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 54)
    - Huth, G., ghostlight, 1990 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 55)
    - Huth, Geof, Haiku Canada Newsletter, Undated (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 56)
    - Huth, G., Interior Definition #2, 1987 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 57)
    - Huth, G., Interior Definition #14, 25 July 1992 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 58)
    - Huth, G., Interior Definitions, 1992 July (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 59)
    - Huth, G., I'ts, 1992 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 60)
    - Huth, G., Magnet, 1988 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 61)
    - Huth, G., May, 1986 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 62)
    - Huth, Geof, "My Tremor", 2005 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 63)
    - Huth, Geof, Pebbleslight, 2002 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 64)
    - Huth, G., Peristyle, 1989 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 65)
    - Huth, G., Peristyle, 1989 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 66)
    - Huth, Geof, Qage, 2005 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 67)
    - Huth, Geof, To a Small Stream of Water, or Ditch, 1992 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 68)
    - Huth, G., Sunset's Wing & Fist Closing Against Eye, 1991 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 69)
    - Huth, G., Things Constantly Moving Against Electric Current, 1992 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 70)
    - Huth, G., Traefik, 1991 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 71)
    - Huth, G., When the Osage Orange, eight colors, 1986 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 72)
    - Huth, G., wreadings, proof copy, 1987 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 73)
    - Huth, G., wreadings, 1987 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 74)
    - Huth, G., wreadings, 2nd Edition, Undated (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 75)
    - Huth, Geof &rbarnes, ?, 1991 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 76)
    - Huth), Ge(of, Is, Mailart, This, Mailart?, published by Rudi Rubberoid, 1989 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 77)
    - Huth, Geof A., Three Pauline Poems, 1990 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 78)
    - I, ca. 1989 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 79)
    - Idioms of æKrete, 2000 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 80)
    - If I Were the Sky, An Anthology of Poems, Stories, Plays and Artwork, Mont Pleasant Middle School, design by Geof Huth, 1993 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 81)
    - Imp Press, Unnamed Leaflets, 2005 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 82)
    - The Imperfect Pitch, Volume 1, #1, 1989 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 83)
    - The Impossible Utterance, #'s1-6, 1990 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 84)
    - Industrial Sabotage, #'s 10, 11, 14, 16-20, 24-26, 29-31, 1982-1985 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 85)
    - Industrial Sabotage, #'s32-39, 1985-1987 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 86)
    - Industrial Sabotage, # 35, 1986 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 87)
    - Industrial Sabotage, #'s 40-50, 1988-1990 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 88)
    - Industrial Sabotage, advertisement flyer for #44, ca. 1989 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 89)
    - Industrial Sabotage, #50, Undated (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 90)
    - Industrial Toilet Paper, #3, 1989 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 91)
    - Infinity, an exhibition of visual poetry and artwork built on/from/around words and letters, 2005 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 92)
    - Insufficient Dada Digest, Undated (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 93)
    - Insufficient Dada Mini, 1991 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 94)
    - Internal Rhyme, 2005 May 27 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 95)
    - III International Biennial of Visual/Experimental/ Alternative, Poetry in Mexico, 1989 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 96)
    - Interstate #1, 9, 1974; 1977 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 97)
    - In the Mail, Undated (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 98)
    - Isin, Serkan, 2005 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 99)
    - Isolation #1-3, 1986 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 100)
    - "It was a", describing an F.A. Nettelbeck performance, ca. 1988 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 101)
    - It's Your Hair, 1990 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 102)
    - Izen, Article of Faith, 1995 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 103)
    - Izen, back to work/to//back to the wall/to, Undated (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 104)
    - Izen, bill of sale/bill of rights, Undated (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 105)
    - Izen, blade of grass/blade of lawnmower, 1993 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 106)
    - Izen, Nothing (Anything), 1993 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 107)
    - Izen, Post Card, 1993 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 108)
    - Izen, round & round, 1993 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 109)
    - Izen, WHOLE, Undated (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 110)
    - Jackpot Years, #1, 1991 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 111)
    - Jane Doe, Volume 4, #1, 1989 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 112)
    - Janet Janet, Schism #20, ca. 1988 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 113)
    - Jannone, John J.A., The Prisoner and the Hermaphrodite, 1993 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 114)
    - Jasper, Matt, Matchbooks, 1989 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 115)
    - Jasper, Matt, Sunlight Floods the Room, Three are Drowned, 1987 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 116)
    - joe, abyss of eye/bus, ca. 1988 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 117)
    - joe, bolton quarterly, #2, 1989 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 118)
    - joe, for pods of the Stuart Sort, 1990 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 119)
    - joe, For Uncle Furuncle, 1990 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 120)
    - joe, four/sum/one, 1990 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 121)
    - joe, straight from the squirrel's mouth/a lament, 19 December 1988 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 122)
    - joe, straight from the squirrel's mouth/a lament, 19 December 1988 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 123)
    - joe, wefish/selfish/goldfish, ca. 1989 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 124)
    - Johnson, Mark, Three Bad Wishes, 1994 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 125)
    - J(o(h)n)ston, brian david, Basho's Narrow Road to the Deep North, 1990 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 126)
    - J(o(h)n)ston, brian david, mute syntax, 2nd edition, 1992 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 127)
    - J(o(h)n)ston, brian david, mute syntax, 1990 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 128)
    - Johnston, Brian David, RAPE, 2 copies signed, 1989 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 129)
    - J(o(h)n)ston, brian david, The Search for (A) Continues, 1990 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 130)
    - The Journal, Volume 12, #2, 1988-1989 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 131)
    - Juniper Jump, #9, mention of Geof Huth, Last page, 1992 (Box 9 (Ho-J) (12-Publications), Folder 132)
    - Kalligram, #12, 2000 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Kansas Quarterly, Volume 20, #3, 1988 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Kathleen K., I Feel as I am Felt, 1986 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 3)
    - katKO, Justin!, CATHECT!, 2005 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 4)
    - katKO, Justin!, SCHEME!, 2005 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Keefe, K.A., Professional Driver, 1989 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Keith, Bill, Wingdom, 1993 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Kelly, John F., A Chance for Adventure, revised edition, 1991 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Kempton, Karl, 33: mathematical poems, 1976-2003 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Kempton, Karl, a/round, 1988 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Kempton, Karl, charged particles, 1991 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Kempton, Karl, film strip lojiktiipoglif ansirz a kweschun, 1983 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Kempton, Karl, fission, 1988 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Kempton, Karl, herring, 1983 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Kempton, Karl, Letterz U Alwayz Wanted to Receeve, 1982 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Kempton, Karl, Poem, 1982 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 16)
    - Kempton, Karl, A Pond of Stars, 1989 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Kempton, Karl, portrait of texture, 1999 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Kempton, Karl, Rose Window, Undated (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Kempton, Karl, Rune 6: Figures of Speech, 1993 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Kempton, Karl, Rune 7: Poem, A Mapping, 1993 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Kempton, Karl, The Voices of Arden, 1993 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Kempton, Ruth & Karl, Fire + Water Balance the Book, inscribed and autographed, 1990 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Kenny, Maurice, Spawning, 1985 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Kentucky Poetry Review, Volume 23, #1, 1987 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Keppler, Joseph, Data, 1985 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Keppler, Joseph, Lesson in Love, ca. 1987 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 27)
    - Keppler, Joseph & David McCleary, NOW, 1985 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 28)
    - Keppler, Joseph, Peace/War, ca. 1987 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 29)
    - Keppler, Joseph, poetic/politic, 1986 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 30)
    - Keppler, Joseph, Poequation Five, 1985 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 31)
    - Keppler, Jacqueline & Joseph, QUARREL, 1988 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 32)
    - Keppler, Joseph, Revolve, 1988 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 33)
    - Kervinen, Jukka-Pekka, fast calf, 2005 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 34)
    - Kervinen, Jukka-Pekka, Templates for John, 2006 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 35)
    - Kervinen, Jukka-Pekka, vote puppet, 2005 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 36)
    - Kettle of Fisk, Volume 1, #'s1-4, 1990 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 37)
    - Kettle of Fisk, Volume 2-Volume 3, 1990 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 38)
    - Kettner, M., father, 1990 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 39)
    - Kettner, M., Full Penny Jar, 1989 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 40)
    - Kettner, M., moments, 1988 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 41)
    - Kettner, M., Polaroid Tavern, 1988 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 42)
    - Key, Bay; Malok; Bennett, John M., Page 1, 1995 September 27 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 43)
    - Kid's World, #2, 4-5, 7-10, 12-13, 18-19, Erin, 1993 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 44)
    - The Killer Whale, Geof Huth & Erin Huth, 1991 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 45)
    - King Suck, 1988 January (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 46)
    - Klimek, Andrew, The Flowers of Mel, 1990 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 47)
    - Kobisena, Outburst 34, 1989 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 48)
    - Kobisena, 40, after 1997 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 49)
    - Kontakte, Series 3, #1, 1986 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 50)
    - Koppany, Marton, Easy meta.com, inscribed to Geof Huth, of an edition of 10, 2004 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 51)
    - Koppany, Marton, Immortality and Freedom, 1987 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 52)
    - Koppany, Marton, The Other Side, 1999 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 53)
    - Kopaska-Merkel, David C., Bad Roberta, 1993 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 54)
    - Kopaska-Merkel, David C., Citizen's Guide to the Barking Dog, ca. 1993 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 55)
    - Kopaska-Merkel, David C., "Every year", 1990 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 56)
    - Kopaska-Merkel, David C., Laetoli, 1990 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 57)
    - Kopaska-Merkel, David C., Phore, Undated (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 58)
    - Kopaska-Merkel, David C., Pockmark, 1993 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 59)
    - Kopaska-Merkel, David C., Recycling with a Bang, 1994 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 60)
    - Kopaska-Merkel, David C., This is a concrete poem, ca. 1992 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 61)
    - Kopaska-Merkel, David C., Toadstool Engineering, 1991 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 62)
    - Kopaska-Merkel, David C., underfoot, introduction by Geof Huth, 1991; 1992 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 63)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, Fields/Pitches/Turfs/Arenas, 1990 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 64)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, Fields/Pitches/Turfs/Arenas, 1990 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 65)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, More partitions, 1994 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 66)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, MORE PARTITONS, 1994 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 67)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, More Wordworks, 2006 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 68)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, Numbers: Poems & Stories, inscribed & signed, 1976 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 69)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, poetry I shall not make, 2003 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 70)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, Recyclings: A Literary Autobiography, 1974 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 71)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, Reincarnations, 1981 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 72)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, Repartitions IV, 1991 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 73)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, Repartitions IV, 1991 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 74)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, Stringtwo, 1989 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 75)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, Wordsand, 1978 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 76)
    - Kostritsky, Gyorgy, æN': Italian Sonnenntina, 2004 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 77)
    - Kostritsky, Gyorgy; Sonnenfeld, Mark, Sonatina Omelet, 2004 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 78)
    - Kovacevic, Mike, Impossibly Tasteful, 1983 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 79)
    - Krysl, Marilyn, Skin, signed, 1987 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 80)
    - Laba, Mark, A History, 1991 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 81)
    - Laba, Mark, and body, 1983 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 82)
    - Laba, Mark, blind, 1986 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 83)
    - Laba, Mark, For David UU, 1987 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 84)
    - Laba, Mark & Joanne Maher, Hats, watches, 1986 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 85)
    - Laba, Mark, Hermaphrodite, 1985 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 86)
    - Laba, Mark, The Misinterpretation, 1983 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 87)
    - Laba, Mark, O, 1984 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 88)
    - Laba, Mark, Sinillogical Translations, Volume 3, 1984 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 89)
    - Laba, Mark, snail tracks, 1984 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 90)
    - Laba, Mark, there, 1990 (Box 10 (K-Lef) (12-Publications), Folder 91)